[Music] It has happened
[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to Option Gyan channel,
friends, today we have
brought this topic, this stock, you all must have
heard its name since childhood, you must have
heard the name of this company, friends, you must have
seen and used its products many times,
but today let's discuss about its stock
and it is time to consider its strength,
hello friends, in the market SMS is at a lifetime high,
all the staff are running, whether it is
all the staff, friends, are you seeing today's time
or today like
Yes Bank was up 12%, Vodafone Idea was
giving a return of 80% within a week, so
friends, there is a huge boom in this stock, there is a
tremendous boom going on and this Africa
stock Maruti is available near Bittu and it is
consolidating here,
yo yo friends, today ITC also touched 67,
now it is showing an upward trend, two months ago
I had to tell my friends that the stock has been
consolidating for a long time and is around two hundred
rupees and right now the stock  You should like it
friends, more than 200, 232 or
within two months, that is,
almost
50% return is being received and the digits
received are different for us, so you
people do not understand this thing that whenever
you get Nifikir stock in the stock, of course there is
momentum in it, it consolidates there,
but when friends, you will see
very quickly, even if you get 10-15% in 2 months, then there is
no harm, so
simple Maruti car friends, friends, there are
three reasons to consider this stock,
one, you will get to learn very good learning here,
I should focus a lot, so the
thing on this is that
friends, all the games in the stock, that is,
Modi's explanation is
moving average, they
consolidate at some place since 2015, this is the
confluence of which, the
price is also consolidating at the same place,
you people must be seeing in the chart
that focus on this place, friends, if you
look carefully, you will see all this at one place
and the price is also at the same place  It is
consolidating around this, friends,
whenever you find this information in any stock, then
you should also tell me by commenting that
it is closed in it, we
will all consider it and in that, friends, till now, the
part which has been my experience, I get
very good profit,
first of all, consolidate all this in one, that is
why I
am updating the system, secondly, friends, it is a
Nifty stock and it is available
near the studio, so it should be liked and shared
and friends, for many days, this stock is
consolidating here, it is necessary in 2018 under 121,
friends, go and check the rate of this thing, you
people were around the local level, but right now
you will get 7000, then I do
not think that you and I should
not choose this topic, friends, if we
look at the share holding pattern in it, then only I will
discuss that with you or you will feel
that this is also the best
and secondly, friends, whenever I give you any
stock, I do not give its target,
that depends on you people,
we  I will leave it till then that
whatever profit you want to book, ten to
fifteen percent, you
can book profit in that and if I
ask you for investment then you can fold it for a long time, so
friends of Maruti stock, you can fold it for a long time also, it
is an investment deal but
if you want to take half this position then I
always give you two-three rates below, so
we will discuss that,
you have to buy this stock at current, that is
600, spy
100,
now friends, although I initially invested 30
% capital, but it is with the stock,
so I can share my 50%
capital here, secondly you have to
cover it at 6545
and below you
cover it at 16 or 237, I will
write it by phone number, that is
6941,
next our base price will be
and the next will be 6237, it will give
three, you should keep this in mind and
go here  We keep sharing with you guys, this is a
good stock, friends, you will
get benefits once we see its share holding
pattern.
Hello friends, the ticket is Pizza, we
see it. Now people definitely know that it is
fundamental. You will go
into details about
getting the ticket. I will
not discuss much about it, today I will
directly focus on the share holding pattern.
Friends, in this you will see
promoter holding 50%, mutual funds
10.47 to
1000, friends
650, that is, retailer stock is very less like this.
All the money that friends,
promoters and all the big institutions are
investing, IDBI etc., is lying with them. If
you see one thing,
friends, in the last quarter, that is,
between March and June, then
retailers are getting free from it
and
DIGs are increasing their positions in it.
So friends, when big institutionals
increase their positions, then why are you people
retreating? You people should
build your position in it. If you get it only near the medium, then
definitely consider it.  I want
sugar, so friends you must have liked my video
and it will be very beneficial for you,
with this hope friends I
end my video, thank you,
so
friends if you like this video then
please do not forget to like, share and subscribe,
thank you for watching my video
[Music]